layoutsexpress.com 2014-04-03

# Free Facebook Layouts, backgrounds and skins for your facebook profile from Layouts Express

## Privacy Policy

Layouts Express (herein “The provider”) is committed to your privacy. Please read our policies below:

The provider recognize the need to protect the privacy of the personal information of our users. Users should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the use of that information.

### No Spyware Policy

The provider never tracks or stores your personaly identifiable information. The browser extension may send unidentifiable and non-personal data. This data is never stored and is used to maintain the correct operation of the offering. Use of the IP address is made to correctly assign weather and language presentation, Utilization of toolbar components determines their correct operation, Use of queries enables and is limited to the correct presentation of shopping component, Use of technical information covering the browser and operating system enables correct functioning of the application, as well as the unique identifier of the browser extension. None of the information is stored or kept on our servers at any time. Information is used immediately as it is gathered to maintain the correct operation of the offering. Information cannot be traced back to the end user. Any information gathered is done on an aggregated basis and in no way can be linked to private information such as private individual name, address, telephone or email, which is never collected or stored.

### No Adware Policy

The provider does not launch pop-up or pop-under advertisement windows or any other type of obtrusive ads. Occasionally users may be presented with advertisements while using the toolbar. We might use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with search results pages may be collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

### Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do so. We use cookies to make it easy for our visitors to download graphics on The provider site. We also use cookies to collect demographic and profile data on an aggregate basis for purposes of delivering content specific to users interests.

### IP addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as "traffic data" so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. The provider will not use your IP address to attempt to identify your personal information.

### Removing the application

Users can easily hide the application by right clicking on the top browser area and then unselecting it from the list. Users can also easily uninstall the application at any time by using the standard uninstall package, by going to Add/Remove Programs in Windows, Add-on Removal in Firefox, etc.

### External links

The application may contain links to third-party Web sites. Please be aware that we cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of third-party Web sites. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies of these Web sites before providing any information to them.

### Data Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Contacting the Provider

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or application, or your dealings with them, you can contact: [privacy@LayoutsExpress.com](mailto:privacy@LayoutsExpress.com)
